SHOSHANAH LO GRECO

Phone: (520) 850-8764 | Email: shoshanahlogreco@gmail.com | Tucson, AZ, 85712

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/shoshanahlogreco | Portfolio: slogreco.github.io | GitHub: github.com/slogreco

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Junior software engineer with two years of background in social media marketing management. Effective at combining systematic organization and creative problem solving skills. Able to quickly develop mutual understanding and trust with clients. Known among staff for strong understanding of software programs and attention to detail no matter the complexity of the project, and recently earned a Certificate in Full Stack Web Development from the University of Arizona.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: CSS, HTML, JavaScript

Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, Sequelize, Mongoose

Tools: Git, Heroku, React, Node.js, Express, Handlebars, jQuery

PROJECTS

Unleash Project | github.com/slogreco/artemis | artemis-project-2.herokuapp.com/

- Contributor for design and function of Indeed for your pets
- JavaScript, Handlebars, MySQL, Sequelize, jQuery, Express, Passport, Morgan

TravelApp | https://github.com/slogreco/dime-travel | slogreco.github.io/dime-travel/

- Front end designer of team project for a site that gives currency exchange with google maps
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bulma, jQuery

Employee Tracker | https://github.com/slogreco/employee-tracker | See ReadMe for Demo

- Sole author of an application that allows an employer to add employees, departments and roles to a SQL database through a node application.
- HTML, JavaScript, Node.js, MySQL, Inquirer

EXPERIENCE

Wellness Key Chiropractic, Tucson, AZ – Chiropractic Assistant

February 2019 - Current

- Develop and manage weekly content for business social media platforms including Facebook, Instagram, YouTube, and weekly email using MailChimp, all the while regularly updating the business website.
- Manage patient appointments, questions, electronic medical records, and general office statistics, ensuring smooth day-to-day operations.

Oregano's Pizza Bistro, Tucson, AZ – Server

January 2018 - November 2018

 Promoted a friendly environment for customers, all the while engaging in teamwork and new server training, while mastering skills in multitasking, and conflict resolution

Hancock Healthcare, Prescott, AZ – Chiropractic Assistant September 2016 - December 2017

Scheduled and confirmed patient appointments, managed patient experiences; all while
multitasking effectively through answering phones, transcribing provider notes, and setting
up and cleaning patient rooms.

EDUCATION

Certificate, Full Stack Development – University of Arizona, Tucson February 2021

Associate Degree, General Studies – Coconino Community College, Flagstaff May 2015